Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Video and Film, 1959 - 1990s
  - Subseries B: Film - Originals
    - Beautiful People - Out-takes and Alt. Titles (B+W), 1988-1989; 092.0108 (Case 092.0108, Reel Film Preservation Release Print 092.0166)
      Footage: [134 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 4 super8mm rolls
    - Beautiful People - Alt. Titles (color), 1988-1989; 092.0109 (Case 092.0109)
      Footage: [65 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 2 super8mm rolls
    - Compilation Reel, [1988 as per edge code]; cuid25991 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0206, Box Shared Fales 119, Super 8mm film reel 092.0110)
      General note
      Footage: [363 ft.]
    - [Mexico Film Footage], [1988 as per edge code]; 092.0111 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0191, Box Shared Fales PM 21, Item 092.0189, Reel Preservation Release Print 092.0188, Item 092.0188, Reel 092.0111, Item 092.0111)
      Footage: 386 ft.
      Duration: 00:19:35
      Description:
    - [Mexico Film Footage II], [1983, 1986 as per edge code]; cuid25993 (Case 092.0112)
      Footage: 74 ft.
    - Mexico, etc... Peter, etc... [as per container], [circa 1986, 1987]; cuid25994 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0201, Case 092.0113)
      Footage: [225 ft.]
      Duration: 00:10:22
    - Fear of Disclosure, The Psycho-social Implications of HIV Revelation, 1988; cuid25995 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0211, Reel 092.0114)
      Format: 16mm
      Footage: [210 ft.]
      Duration: [00:05:00]
    - Where Evil Dwells - Camera Original I, [undated]; cuid25996 (Case 092.0115)
      Footage: [400 ft.]
    - Where Evil Dwells - Camera Original II, [undated]; cuid25997 (Case 092.0116)
    - [New York Cultural Centre Annex Performance], [undated]; cuid25998 (Case 092.0117)
      Footage: 263 ft.
    - [Rolls 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8], [undated]; cuid25999 (Case 092.0118)
      Footage: 401 ft. 49 frames
    - [Rolls 9,10,11], [undated]; cuid26000 (Case 092.0119)
      Footage: 149 ft. 70 frames
    - [Rolls 17,18,19], [undated]; cuid26001 (Case 092.0120)
      Footage: 150 ft. 46 frames
    - [Anti-Gay Bigots, Misc Footage], [1986 as per edge code]; cuid26002 (Case 092.0121)
      Footage: 149 ft.
    - [Frog Dance, etc.], [undated]; cuid26003 (Reel 092.0122)
      Footage: 522 ft.
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel III], [circa mid-1980s]; cuid26004 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0206, Case 092.0123)
      Footage: 93 ft. 35 frames
      Duration: 00:04:55
    - A Fire in My Belly, [circa 1985]; cuid26005 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0179, Box Shared Fales 119, Super 8mm film reel 092.0124)
      Footage: 262 ft. 24 frames
      Duration: [00:12:00]
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel], [late 1980s]; cuid26006 (Case 092.0125)
      Footage: 206 ft. 65 frames
    - [Howdy Doody Footage I], [undated]; 092.0126 (Case 092.0126)
      Footage: 360 ft. 66 frames
    - [Howdy Doody Footage II], [undated]; 092.0127 (Case 092.0127)
      Footage: 202 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody Footage III], [undated]; 092.0128 (Case 092.0128)
      Footage: 388 ft.
    - Heroin, 1981; cuid26010 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0185, Box Shared Fales 119, Super 8mm film reel 092.0133)
      Footage: 51 ft.
      Duration: [00:02:50]
    - [Peter Hujar - Rolls], [undated]; cuid26011 (Case 092.0136, Super 8mm film reel cuid26011)
      Footage: [350 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 6 super8mm rolls
    - [Heroin - Unedited Color Footage], [circa 1979]; cuid26012 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 092.0378, Case 092.0146)
      Footage: [340 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 7 super8mm rolls
    - [Cockfights], [1986]; cuid26013 (Case 092.0147)
      Footage: [175 ft.]
    - [Out Sarah's Window; Demolition Derby], [undated]; cuid26014 (Case 092.0148)
    - [Nature, Water, Swamp], [1987]; cuid26015 (Case 092.0149)
      Footage: [425 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 9 super8mm rolls
    - [Rain/Mammals], [1981,1987]; cuid26016 (Case 092.0150)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 10 super8mm rolls
    - [Gorillas, Elephants, Waves, Sky], [1986,1987]; cuid26017 (Case 092.0151)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 7 super8mm rolls]
    - [Cavern Point/Driving Shots], [1987, 1983]; cuid26018 (Case 092.0152)
      Footage: [275 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 5 super8mm rolls
    - [Misc. B+W Shots], [1983,1986,1987]; cuid26019 (Case 092.0153)
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 8 super8mm rolls
    - [Ants] (color), [1986,1987,1988]; cuid26020 (Case 092.0154)
      Footage: [160 ft.]
    - [Swamp/Skeleton] (color), [1985, unknown]; cuid26021 (Case 092.0155)
      Footage: [240 ft.]
    - [Driving, Sky, and Misc. Shots], [undated]; cuid26022 (Case 092.0156)
      Footage: [290 ft.]
    - [Fire Boys, Ants, and Mexico Themes], [1981,1984,1986,1987]; cuid26023 (Case 092.0157)
      Footage: [300 ft.]
    - [Unidentified Film w/ David Wojnarowicz], [undated]; 092.0158 (Reel 092.0158)
      Footage: 128 ft.
    - [Nite Scenes w/ David W.(Neg); Centaur Films], [undated]; 092.0159 (Reel 092.0159)
      Footage: 102 ft. 6 frames
    - Manhattan Love Suicides by R. Kern, 1984; 092.0212 (Box 199, Item 092.0212, Box Shared Fales PM 21, Item 091.0071)
      Source Format: [Super8mm]
    - [Aeroport/ Train Lines/ Gary/ Rail Landscapes/ Bercy], [Crows], [Bercy Windows, Stones/ Fire], [A) Morphologies, Restaurant Cafe 2], [B) Morphologies, Restaurant Cafe 2], 1984; cuid41268 (Reel 092.0213)
      Silent, black and white images of abandoned buildings, crows in trees, a man (Gary Indiana) looking out the window of a train, and David Wojnarowicz in a cafe. The footage was taken in and around Paris, France in the Winter of 1984.
      Source Format: Super 8mm film
      Duration: 12 min. 30 sec.
      Preservation Note: These films were donated as undeveloped Super8mm film cartridges. In 2019, NYU Special Collections facilitated an effort to process and digitally scan the works. The five films were were combined into a single reel and accessed via a single digital file. Photographs of the original cartridges are preserved with the digital file and available upon request.
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 90, undated; cuid26032 (Box 90)
      092.0106-092.0123
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 91, undated; cuid26033 (Box 91)
      092.0124-092.0128, 092.0133, 092.0136, 092.0146-092.0149 C
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 92, undated; cuid26034 (Box 92)
      092.0149 D-092.0154
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 93, undated; cuid26035 (Box 93)
      092.0155-092.0157, 092.0160, 092.0162, plus 7 unnumbered folders
    - Annotated Film Containers Box 94, undated; cuid26036 (Box 94)
      (Trailer) 1986, N.Y.C, D. Wojnarowicz 228-7024; 092.00158-092.0159 "Nite Scenes w/ David W.; Envelope For Film, "Kin-O-Lux, Inc. - David Wojnarowicz"
    - Lists and notes on film and video content, cuid26076 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Subseries C: Film - Access Prints
    Subseries C: Film - Access Prints contains completed film works plus original source material by David Wojnarowicz originally on Super8mm preserved on 16mm.
    - [Heroin - Unedited Color Footage], [circa 1979]; ID: 092.0175 (Box Shared Fales 048, Reel 092.0175)
      Original Format:
    - Heroin, 1981; ID: 092.0132 (Reel 092.0132)
      Footage: [92 ft.]
    - [Untitled Wojnarowicz Compilation Reel III], [circa mid-1980s]; ID: 092.0203 (Reel 092.0203)
      Footage: [209 ft.]
    - [Mexico Film Footage II], [1983, 1986 as per Super8 edge code]]; ID: 092.0193 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 092.0193, Box Shared Fales 124, Dvd 092.0196)
      Footage: [179 ft.]
      Duration: 00:04:05
    - Mexico, etc... Peter, etc... [as per original container], [circa 1986, 1987]; ID: 092.0198 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 092.0198, Box Shared Fales 124, Dvd 092.0201)
      Footage: [405 ft.]
    - A Fire in My Belly, 1986-1987 (work in progress); ID: 092.0130 (Reel 092.0130)
      Footage: [470 ft.]
      Duration: [00:13:05]
    - [Mexico Film Footage], [1988 as per Super8 edge code]; ID: 092.0188 (Reel Preservation Release Print 092.0188, Box 124, Dvd 092.0191)
      Footage: [736 ft.]
    - Beautiful People, 1988-1989; ID: 092.0164 (Reel Film Preservation Release Print 092.0164)
      Footage: [1400 ft.]
      Duration: [00:38:00]
    - Beautiful People - B+W Extras (Out-takes and Alt. Titles), 1988-1989; ID: 092.0166 (Reel Film Preservation Release Print 092.0166)
      Footage: [380 ft.]
      Duration: [00:11:00]
    - Beautiful People - Color Extras (Out-takes and Alt. Titles), 1988-1989; cuid41065 (Box Shared Fales 119, 16mm film reels 092.0168)
      Footage: [335 ft.]
      Duration: [00:10:00]
      Preservation note: This is a 2005 preservation print which duplicates cuid41066 and additional related material from another reel or reels.
    - [Footage for Film About Peter Hujar], [undated]; ID: 092.0135 (Reel 092.0135)
      Footage: [600 ft.]
      Description: compilation reel consisting of 6 super 8mm rolls
    - [Footage For Film About Peter Hujar] (Box Shared Fales 124, Dvd 092.0182)
      Duration: [00:15:30]
      Description: This negative is a 16mm blow-up of original Super 8mm elements.
    - Where Evil Dwells, [undated]; ID: 092.0139 (Reel 092.0139, Box 200, Dvd 092.0500)
      Footage: [1150 ft.]
      Duration: [00:28:00]
      Original Format: Super8mm film
    - [Howdy Doody #120], [undated]; ID: 092.0141 (Reel 092.0141)
      Footage: 330 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody #119], [undated]; ID: 092.0143 (Reel 092.0143)
      Footage: 659 ft.
    - [Howdy Doody #121], [undated]; ID: 092.0145 (Reel 092.0145)
      Footage: 706 ft.
    - [Swamp/Skeletons], [undated]; ID: 092.0169 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 092_0169)
      Duration: 00:13:00
    - [Ants] (color), [undated]; ID: 092.0171 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 092.0171)
      Duration: 00:08:00
    - [Driving, Sky, and Misc. Shots], [undated]; ID: 092.0173 (Reel 092.0173)
  - Subseries D: Commercial Video by Others
    Subseries D: Commercial Works by Others contains recordings that made up David Wojnarowicz's personal collection.
    - Anita Dances of Vice, by Rosa von Praunheim, VHS tape (Dub), undated; cuid26037 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Bayard Rustin, by Phil Zwickler, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26038 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - The Critical Years / The Grace of God, by Gerald Lecuyer, 40 min. VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26039 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Excerpts from: Blind Prosperity / Money Talk, by Gloria McLean & Ben Neill, Teliospore, by Gloria McLean, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26040 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Fedora / Laura, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26041 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Fingered, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, undated; cuid26042 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Game Set Match, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26043 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Genet / Harvey Milk, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26044 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes, Twentieth Century Fox, VHS tape, undated; cuid26045 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - How to Marry a Millionaire, Twentieth Century Fox, VHS tape, undated; cuid26046 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - How to Shoot a Crime, by Kraus, (Chris?) 26 min. VHS tape, undated; cuid26047 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - La Belle et La Bete / Visages de Femmes, VHS tape, undated; cuid26048 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - La Dolce Vita, Pt. I, by Federico Fellini, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26049 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - La Dolce Vita, Pt. II, by Federico Fellini, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26050 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Lawrence of Arabia, Columbia Pictures, Pts. 1-2, 2 VHS tapes, undated; cuid26051 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Manhattan love Suicides w/ Bill Rice & D. Wojnarowicz, b&w, 30 min. VHS tape, undated; cuid26052 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Maria Callas: Hamburg Concert 1959, Kuktur, VHS, cuid26053 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Mondo Cane / Macbeth (Kurosawa) / Sting in Tokyo, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26054 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Mother Theresa, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26055 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Mr. Hulot's Holiday, by Jacques Tati, & other video, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26056 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Never on Sunday, MGM, UA, VHS tape, undated; cuid26057 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Pursuit of Happiness (Malle) / La Strada / Stranger Than Paradise, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26058 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Quilt, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26059 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - The Red Hot Organization / No Alternative, Nov 1993, VHS tape (dub), cuid26060 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Red Hot & Blue: A Tribute to Cole Porter to Benefit AIDS Research and Relief, Arista, 1990, VHS tape, cuid26061 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Rev. Howard Finster, Man of Vision, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26062 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - The Right Side of My Brain, by Richard Kern, 30 min. Betamax tape, undated; cuid26063 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Rumblefish, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26064 (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Sex vs. Guns, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, undated; cuid26065 (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Stop the Church, by Robert Hilferty, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26066 (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Submit to Me / Death Valley '69 / You Killed Me First, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, 1969; cuid26067 (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Submit to Me / Death Valley '69 / You Killed Me First, by Richard Kern, VHS tape, 1969; cuid26068 (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Tom Rubnitz, Video Director: various, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26069 (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - A Virus Knows No Morals, by Rosa von Praunheim, First Run Features, 84 minute VHS tape, undated; cuid26070 (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - Where Evil Dwells, by Wojnarowicz & Turner, VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26071 (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - The Young Ones (various series episodes), VHS tape (dub), undated; cuid26072 (Box 97, Folder 36)
- Series XI: Art Works, circa 1970s - 1990s
  This series includes sketches, drawings, studies, altered items, and collage; source material comprises diverse images and textual material which bear directly and indirectly on Wojnarowicz's art. Such items as maps, comic books, postcards, tear sheets, decals, and targets appear in the source material. Art by others includes work by downtown contemporaries Kiki Smith and Barbara Kruger.
  This series is arranged into seven subseries: Subseries A: Finished/Original; Subseries B: Drawings; Subseries C: Sketches; Subseries D: Source/Background Material; Subseries E: Plans; Subseries F: Xerox Art; and Subseries G: Other People's Art.
  - Subseries A: Finished/Original
    - Art - blue ballpoint pen drawing - "Look Honey a Hallucination", undated; cuid27019 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Art - color separation, undated; cuid27020 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Art Sketch Book - "Bowery Joe", undated; cuid27021 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Art - 2 prints - Brain-Time, undated; cuid27022 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Art - production - color sample - The Death of American Spirituality, undated; cuid27023 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Art - production - color separation - The Death of American Spirituality, undated; cuid27024 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Art - black ink, undated; cuid27025 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Art - frottage, undated; cuid27026 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Art - images and text, undated; cuid27027 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Art - "Mexico" collage, undated; cuid27028 (Box 148, Folder 9B.)
    - Art - "I Have Always Liked...the Idea of Movies. .", undated; cuid27029 (Box 148, Folder 9C.)
    - Art and Images - Memories that Smell Like Gasoline, undated; cuid27030 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Art and Poem - graphite pencil drawing of dog with cast, undated; cuid27031 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Art - Peter Hujar's diagnostic letter altered with a drawing of two men kissing, from W's "Fuck You Faggot-Hater" series, undated; cuid27032 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Art - transparency, "Buying Souls. .", undated; cuid27033 (Box 148, Folder 12A.)
    - Art - Xerox diptych, undated; cuid27034 (Box 148, Folder 9A.)
    - Comic collage, undated; cuid27035 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Comic - altered Archie comic: "Yo Sadie. .", undated; cuid27036 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Comic - altered Archie comic: "Reggie is trying to kick his junk habit again. .", undated; cuid27037 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Comic - altered Archie comic: "Archie and Mr. Weatherbee in 'School Tool'", cuid27038 (Box 148, Folder 15A.)
    - Folder with sperm art - painted collage on manilla folder, undated; cuid27039 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Image - brain, eye, earth, heart, undated; cuid27040 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Images, undated; cuid27041 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Man's face in shadow, undated; cuid27042 (Box 148, Folder 18A.)
    - Postcard - altered, undated; cuid27043 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Rimbaud mask, undated; cuid27044 (Box 115)
    - Sperm/Money/Seeds w/envelope, undated; cuid27045 (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Stencils - Burning House, Undated; cuid6194; 1 item one stencil (Box 112, Object MSS.092.cuid6194)
      Stencils (image-making tools)
    - Stencils - Falling Man, undated; cuid28575
    - Burning man running, Undated; cuid6199; 1 item one poster (Item MSS.092.cuid6199)
      Works of art.
  - Subseries B: Drawings
    [see also Flat Box]
    - Bee: "I'm gonna hold my breath until I die", undated; cuid27046 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Bellevue Hospital, sketches from, undated; cuid27047 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Bread loaf sewn, ape with club, etc., undated; cuid27048 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Crashing dove, large deer with leg through roof of house, etc., undated; cuid27049 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Fuck You Bozo, undated; cuid27050 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - recordings after sleep, undated; cuid27051 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Two men with trousers down, undated; cuid27052 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Water, drawings from, undated; cuid27053 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Various drawings, undated; cuid27054 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Subseries C: Sketches
    - Sketchbook, undated; cuid27055 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Sketchpad, undated; cuid27056 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Storyboard for Times Square Project, undated; cuid27057 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: Source/Background Material
    - Ads in Spanish, undated; cuid27058 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Archives of American Art materials, undated; cuid27059 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Article on bullfrog, undated; cuid27060 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Article on prison in Newsweek (Oct. 6, 1986), cuid27061 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Autumn leaf cut-outs, undated; cuid27062 (Box 148, Folder 4A.)
    - Cards, undated; cuid27063 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Cards - French, undated; cuid27064 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Cards - pictures of animals, undated; cuid27065 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Cards - postcards and envelopes, undated; cuid27066 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Cards - postcards (may contain notes), undated; cuid27067 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Cards - postcards, undated; cuid27068 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Clippings and tearsheets, undated; cuid27069 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, undated; cuid27070 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, undated; cuid27071 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Comics, undated; cuid27072 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Ripley's Believe it or Not Collection, A Guide, 1978., cuid27073 (Box 149, Folder 14A)
    - Exploded Views, Completely Detailed Drawings of Famous Firearms, undated; cuid27074 (Box 149, Folder 14B)
    - Comics, undated; cuid27075 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Comics, undated; cuid27076 (Box 149, Folder 15A.)
    - Comics, undated; cuid27077 (Box 149, Folder 15B.)
    - Comics, undated; cuid27078 (Box 149, Folder 15C.)
    - Comics, undated; cuid27079 (Box 149, Folder 15D.)
    - Coupons, undated; cuid27080 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Decals, undated; cuid27081 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Diagram of eye, undated; cuid27082 (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - Diagram of frog, undated; cuid27083 (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - Envelopes, undated; cuid27084 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - Flag images on felt, undated; cuid27085 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - Holograms, undated; cuid27086 (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - Maps, undated; cuid27087 (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Maps, undated; cuid27088 (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - Maps, undated; cuid27089 (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Maps, undated; cuid27090 (Box 149, Folder 26)
    - Mexican wrestling magazines, undated; cuid27091 (Box 149, Folder 26A.)
    - Night Train label, undated; cuid27092 (Box 149, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, undated; cuid27093 (Box 149, Folder 28)
    - Plastic rulers, undated; cuid27094 (Box 149, Folder 28A.)
    - Pornography - cards and tearsheets, undated; cuid27095 (Box 149, Folder 29)
    - Pornography - "Old Reliable" catalog, undated; cuid27096 (Box 149, Folder 30)
    - Poster: "Jibaro Si! Yankkkee No.", undated; cuid27097 (Box 149, Folder 30A.)
    - Printed material, undated; cuid27098 (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Signs, undated; cuid27099 (Box 149, Folder 32)
    - Signs - FBI Wanted, undated; cuid27100 (Box 149, Folder 33)
    - Signs - missing animal, undated; cuid27101 (Box 149, Folder 34)
    - Signs - police posting, undated; cuid27102 (Box 149, Folder 35)
    - Source - assorted print material, undated; cuid27103 (Box 149, Folder 36)
    - Source, undated; cuid27104 (Box 108, Folder 37)
    - Source, undated; cuid27105 (Box 108, Folder 38)
    - Stencils - alphabet & numbers, undated; cuid27106 (Box 108, Folder 39)
    - Targets - animals, undated; cuid27107 (Box 108, Folder 40)
    - Targets - bull's eye, undated; cuid27108 (Box 108, Folder 41)
    - Text on acetate, undated; cuid27109 (Box 108, Folder 42)
  - Subseries E: Plans
    - Various plans, undated; cuid27110 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Subseries F: Xerox Art
    - Black and white, undated; cuid27111 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Black marker drawings, undated; cuid27112 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Color, undated; cuid27113 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Color (cont'd), undated; cuid27114 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - FBI and police notices, undated; cuid27115 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Finished works by DW xeroxed, undated; cuid27116 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Man with gun, undated; cuid27117 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Money, undated; cuid27118 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Self-portrait with target, undated; cuid27119 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Subseries G: Other People's Art
    - Other people's art - various, undated; cuid27120 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Series XII: Library, 1892-1994
  This series lists the books and other printed items that were in Wojnarowicz's library when it arrived at Fales. They were removed from the archive; most titles have been cataloged and can be retrieved by searching Bobcat, the Bobst library's online catalog.
  Many items may be considered source material, as a significant portion of the content is reflected in the motifs and preoccupations expressed in Wojnarowicz's art.
  - Abe, Kobo. Secret Rendezvous. Trans. Juliet Winters Carpenter. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1979., cuid27121 (Box XII.1, Folder 1)
  - Abbot, Jack Henry. In the Belly of the Beast. New York: Vintage, 1991., cuid27122 (Box XII.1, Folder 2)
  - Abrahams, Roger D., ed. African Folktales: Traditional Stories of the Black World. New York: Pantheon, 1983., cuid27123 (Box XII.1, Folder 3)
  - Acker, Kathy. The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula, by the Black Tarantula. New York: TVRT Press, 1978., cuid27124 (Box XII.1, Folder 4)
  - ---. Hello, I'm Erica Jong. New York: Contact II Publications, 1982., cuid27125 (Box XII.1, Folder 5)
  - ---. In Memoriam to Identity. London: Pandora, 1990., cuid27126 (Box XII.1, Folder 6)
  - ---. Implosion. New York: Wedge Press, 1983., cuid27127 (Box XII.1, Folder 7)
  - ---. Literal Madness. New York: Grove, 1988., cuid27128 (Box XII.1, Folder 8)
  - Ades, Dawn. Photomontage. London: Thames and Hudson, 1976., cuid27129 (Box XII.1, Folder 9)